A Guide to the Iron Gate, Virginia, Ledgers, 1892-1931
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Iron Gate, Virginia, Ledgers, 1892-1931
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2012-068
1.7 cu. ft. 2 boxes
The collection consists of 23 ledgers and day books, as well as approximately 60 receipts and other loose documents relating to a general goods store in Iron Gate, Virginia.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The collection was purchased by Special Collections in July 2011.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of 23 ledgers and day books, as well as approximately 60 receipts and other loose documents relating to a general goods store in Iron Gate, Virginia. Loose documents include correspondence, business contracts, advertisements, brochures, other business records, receipts, and ephemera. Ledgers consist of a small ledger and order book, inventories and sold items, balance sheets, real estate taxes, ledger credit scrip, daily ledgers, and personal accounts.
Arrangement
Box 1 is arranged by type of material. Box 2 is arranged chronologically and by type of material.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South
Contents List
- Correspondence (Box-folder 1-1)
- Business Contracts, Advertisements, Brochures, and other business records (Box-folder 1-2)
- Receipts (Box-folder 1-3)
- American Redcross Membership Forms (Box-folder 1-4)
- Small Ledger and Order Book (1897) (Box-folder 1-5)
- Hats Sold -- Spring and Summer (1922) (Box-folder 1-6)
- Inventory and Sold Items (1897-1903 and 1919-1925) (Box-folder 1-7)
- Balance Sheets (1924-1931) (Box-folder 1-8)
- List of Real Estate Taxes (1893-1896) (Box-folder 2-1)
- Ledger Credit Scrip (1898-1901) (Box-folder 2-2)
- Ledger Credit Scrip (1901-1916) (Box-folder 2-3)
- Daily Ledgers (1897-1901) (Box-folder 2-4)
- Daily Ledgers (1901-1902) (Box-folder 2-5)
- Daily Ledgers (1902-1905) (Box-folder 2-6)
- Daily Ledgers (1905-1906 and 1912-1915) (Box-folder 2-7)
- Personal Accounts (1892-1893) (Box-folder 2-8)
- Personal Accounts (1894-1896) (Box-folder 2-9)
- Personal Accounts (1896-1900) (Box-folder 2-10)
- Personal Accounts (1903-1907) (Box-folder 2-11)
- Personal Accounts (1915-1918) (Box-folder 9-12)
- Personal Accounts (1918-1921) (Box-folder 9-13)
- Personal Accounts (1925-1928) (Box-folder 2-14)
- Ephemera (Box-folder 2-15)